Pintye Dávid davpintye@gmail.com +36308440030 https://github.com/Davi-hub https://linkedin.com/in/david-pintye

1139 Budapest



Self Definition

I've been close to the IT world since I was a kid, but I have been studying Web Development at higher levels for two years. I have acquired my knowledge by myself, mostly in English. The majority of my skills is related to front-end technologies, but I have also written smaller programs in Node.js, Java and Python. I am highly motivated to be part of larger projects in a work environment as a Junior Web Developer.

Strength

I like creating new, useful things. I am persistent, enthusiastic and try to do my job to the best of my ability. I prefer to work independently, but I also like working in a team. Most of my experience is related to the Angular framework. I am interested in all areas of IT and it is also my hobby.

Work Experience

Employee (2018-2021)

Construction work

Participation in various interior design projects, including painting, furniture design, manufacturing, assembly, and other related tasks.

Contributor (2016-2017)

Mol Hungary - Record Office

Digitization of drilling documents.

Intern (2016-2017)

Mol Hungary - H.S.E.

Consolidation, formatting update, verification, and preparation for release of the identical subject area HSE regulations.

Educations

Career Starter Kit course (2022-2022)

Codecool

Environmental Engineering Bsc (2013-2017)

Budapest University of Technology and Economics

(Did not obtain a degree.)

Mathematics and IT (2006-2010)

Csokonai Vitéz Mihály High School, Debrecen

Spoken Languages

English - Intermediate

German - Basic

Hungarian - Native

Hobbies









Arduino



Pi. Cvclii